questions = [
    {
        question: "The man _______ is standing next to my mother is my uncle.",
        answers: ["that", "which", "who"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "_______ cat is absolutely beautiful.",
        answers: ["They’re", "There", "Their"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "______ shoes that I’m wearing right now are so comfortable.",
        answers: ["This", "These", "Those"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "The dog is chasing _____ tail.",
        answers: ["it’s", "its", "that’s"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "She has five _______.",
        answers: ["child", "childrens", "children"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "The ____________ are in the field.",
        answers: ["horse’s", "horse is", "horses"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "________ hair looks really nice.",
        answers: ["You’re", "Your", "Yours"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Mary has ______ brothers.",
        answers: ["to", "too", "two"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "She is better in sports _____ him.",
        answers: ["then", "than", "that"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "_______ did you invite to your birthday party?",
        answers: ["Who", "Whom", "Whose"],
        correct: 1
    }

]
module.exports = ({
    questions
})
